You know, y'all think I'm just going on and on about Kamala, but what you're failing to realize
is this is a conversation. This is a exchange about ethics. I mean, she is merely the tool
being used to leverage this conversation, but that's what this conversation really is. It's
one about ethics and morals and what principles people are willing to ignore and why. So when
you see Kamala Harris being the center of conversation, it's because this is a very
critical moment that really identifies different people's values. It identifies what ethics mean
for people. And if genocide as clearly defined as it is still allows for people's ethics to
waver, then it gives you an idea of where we are culturally as a people in terms of bottom
lines. So when folks ask for like solutions and what can we do, it's like, well, you can't
do shit when people's values and ethics and principles are in the gutter because those
aren't people that you can depend on. Those aren't people that you can trust. Those aren't
people that you can build with and know that they won't get wavy when it suits them the way
that they have gotten wavy about a genocide when it suits them.